Guide to the Stanford University, Press, Archival Book Copies
Stanford University. Libraries.
- 2004
  - Erie, Steven P, Globalizing L.A.; trade, infrastructure, and regional development., 2004 (Box 5)
  - Faure, Bernard, Double exposure: cutting across Buddhist and Western discourses., 2004 (Box 5)
  - Fields, Gary, Terrorities of profit., 2004 (Box 5)
  - Fisher, William W, Promises to keep: technology, law, and the future of entertainment., 2004 (Box 5)
  - Fong, Vanessa L, Only hope; coming of age under China's one-child policy., 2004 (Box 5)
  - Fraser, Sarah H, Performing the visual: the practice of Buddhist wall painting in China and Central Asia, 618-960., 2004 (Box 5)
  - Freadman, Anne, The Machinery of talk., 2004 (Box 6)
  - Fuess, Harald, Divorce in Japan; family, gender, and the state 1600-2000., 2004 (Box 6)
  - Gallagher, Kevin, Free trade and the environment., 2004 (Box 6)
  - Geiger, Roger L., 1943-, Knowledge and money: research universities and the paradox of the marketplace., 2004 (Box 6)
  - Gelfand, Michele J., ed, The handbook of negotiation and culture., 2004 (Box 6)
  - Genet, Jean, The declared enemy; texts and interviews., 2004 (Box 6)
  - Gill, Indermit S., Truman Packard and Juan Yermo, Keeping the Promise of Social Security in Latin America., 2004 (Box 6)
  - Gillmor, C. Stewart, Fred Terman at Stanford: Building a Discipline, a University, and Silicon Valley., 2004 (Box 6)
  - Girard, Rene, Oedipus Unbound; selected writings on rivalry and desire., 2004 (Box 6)
  - Green, Arthur, A Guide to the Zohar., 2004 (Box 7)
  - Guillet de Monthoux, Pierre, The Art Firm; aesthetic management and metaphysical marketing from Wagner to Wilson., 2004 (Box 7)
  - Guinnane, Timothy, et. al., eds, History Matters., 2004 (Box 7)
  - Gumbrecht, Hans Ulrich, Production of presence; what meaning cannot convey., 2004 (Box 7)
  - Haidu, Peter, The subject medieval / modern., 2004 (Box 7)
  - Harshaw, Benjamin, Marc Chagall and his times; a documentary narrative., 2004 (Box 7)
  - Hazard, Geoffrey C, Legal ethics: a comparative study., 2004 (Box 7)
  - Heith, Diane J, Polling to govern: public opinion and presidential leadership., 2004 (Box 7)
  - Howard, Joshua H, Workers at War: Labor in China's Arsenals, 1937-1953., 2004 (Box 8)
  - Ikels, Charlotte, ed, Filial Piety; practice and discourse in contemporary East Asia., 2004 (Box 8)
  - Jacobs, Andrew S, Remains of the Jews; the Holy Land and Christian empire in late antiquity., 2004 (Box 8)
  - Kenney, Martin, ed, Locating global advantage., 2004 (Box 8)
  - Kim, Hodong, Holy War in China., 2004 (Box 8)
  - Kinney, Anne Behnke, Representations of childhood and youth in early China., 2004 (Box 8)
  - Kirby, William C., Realms of freedom in modern China., 2004 (Box 8)
  - Koeneke, Rodney, Empires of the mind; I.A. Richards and basic English in China, 1929-1979., 2004 (Box 8)
  - Koshy, Susan, Sexual Naturalization: Asian Americans and Miscegenation., 2004 (Box 8)
  - Kouri, Emilio, A Pueblo Divided: Business, Property, and Community in Papantla Mexico., 2004 (Box 9)
  - Krauss, Ellis S., ed, Beyond bilateralism: U.S.-Japan relations in the new Asia-Pacific., 2004 (Box 9)
  - Kritzer, Herbert M, Risks, reputations, and rewards: contingency fee legal practice in the United States., 2004 (Box 9)
  - Kurz, Karin, ed., Home ownership and social inequality in comparative perspective., 2004 (Box 9)
  - Laing, Ellen Johnston and Helen Hui-Ling Liu, Up in flames; the ephemeral art of pasted-paper sculpture in Taiwan., 2004 (Box 9)
  - Liu, Xiaoyuan, Frontier passages; ethnopolitics and the rise of Chinese communism, 1921-1945., 2004 (Box 9)
  - Louie, Vivian S, Compelled to excel: immigration, education, and pportunity among Chinese Americans., 2004 (Box 9)
  - MacAvoy, Paul W, The recurrent crisis in corporate governance., 2004 (Box 9)
  - Majid, Anouar, Freedom and orthodoxy; Islam and difference in the post-andalusian age., 2004 (Box 9)
  - Malabou, Catherine, Counterpath: traveling with Jacques Derrida., 2004 (Box 9)
  - Man-Cheong, Iona D, The class of 1761: examinations, State, and elites in eighteeenth-century China., 2004 (Box 10)
  - Marion, Jean-Luc, The Crossing of the Visible., 2004 (Box 10)
  - Matt, Daniel C., transl. & ed, The Zohar. Vol 1 and 2., 2004 (Box 10)
  - Mazlish, Bruce, Civilization and its Contents., 2004 (Box 10)
  - McGann, Frank D, Soldiers of the Patria; a history of the Brazilian Army, 1889-1937., 2004 (Box 10)
  - McLean, Stuart, The event and its terrors: Ireland, famine, modernity., 2004 (Box 10)
  - Micale, Mark S., ed, The mind of modernism., 2004 (Box 10)
  - Miceli, Thomas J, Economic approach to law., 2004 (Box 10)
  - Michaud, Eric, The cult of art in Nazi Germany., 2004 (Box 11)
  - Miyazaki, Hirokazu, The method of hope: anthropology, philosophy, and Fjian knowledge., 2004 (Box 11)
  - Morris, Irwin L., et. al., eds, Politics from Anarchy to Democracy., 2004 (Box 11)
  - Mowery, David C., et. al, Ivory Tower and Industrial Innovation., 2004 (Box 11)
  - Paletschek, Sylvia, ed, Women's emancipation movements in the 19th century., 2004 (Box 11)
  - Paul, T.V., et. al., eds, Balance of power: theory and practice in the 21st century., 2004 (Box 11)
  - Peck, Mary and Charles Wilkinson, Away Out Over Everything: The Olympic Peninsula and the Elwha River., 2004 (Box 11)
  - Peperzak, Adriaan T, Elements of ethics., 2004 (Box 11)
  - Pieke, Frank N., et. al, Transnational Chinese; Fujianese migrants in Europe., 2004 (Box 11)
  - Ranciere, Jacques, The flesh of words: the politics of writing., 2004 (Box 11)
  - Rao, Vijayendra, Culture and public action., 2004 (Box 12)
  - Rogers-Dillon, Robin H, Welfare Experiments; politics and policy evaluation., 2004 (Box 12)
  - Rosenfeld, Maya, Confronting the occupation: work, education, and political activism of Palestinian families in a refugee camp., 2004 (Box 12)
  - Rossler, Beate, ed, Privacies; philosophical evaluations., 2004 (Box 12)
  - Ruggiero, Kristin, Modernity in the flesh., 2004 (Box 12)
  - Salomon, Nanette, Shifting priorities: gender and genre in seventeenth-century Dutch painting., 2004 (Box 12)
  - Samet, Elizabeth D, Willing Obedience; Citizens, soldiers, and the progress of consent in America, 1776-1898., 2004 (Box 12)
  - Sandler, Stephanie, Commemorating Pushkin, Russia's myth of a national poet., 2004 (Box 12)
  - Scheingold, Stuart A, Something to believe in: politics, professionalism, and cause lawyering., 2004 (Box 12)
  - Schnapp, Jeffrey T, Building Fascism, Communism, Liberal Democracy., 2004 (Box 13)
  - Seaver, Kirsten A., 1934-, Maps, myths, and men: the story of the Vinland map., 2004 (Box 13)
  - Shao, Qin, Culturing modernity: the Nantong model, 1890-1930., 2004 (Box 13)
  - Shryock, Andrew, Off stage/on display: intimacy and ethnography in the age of public culture., 2004 (Box 13)
  - Simpson, Lee M. A, Selling the city: gender, class, and the California growth machine, 1880-1940., 2004 (Box 13)
  - Sjoholm, Cecilia, The Antigone Complex: Ethics and the Invention of Feminine Desire., 2004 (Box 13)
  - Solis, Mireya, Banking on multinationals: public credit and the export of Japanese sunset industries., 2004 (Box 13)
  - Stablein, Ralph E., ed, Renewing research practice., 2004 (Box 13)
  - Street, Richard Steven, Photographing farmworkers in California., 2004 (Box 14)
  - Street, Richard Steven, Beasts of the field: a narrative history of California farmworkers, 1769-1913., 2004 (Box 13)
  - Suh, J.J.. et. al, eds, Rethinking security in East Asia: identity, power, and efficiency., 2004 (Box 14)
  - Takeuchi, Melinda, ed, The artist as professional in Japan., 2004 (Box 14)
  - Taubes, Jacob, The political theology of paul., 2004 (Box 14)
  - Thornton, Patricia H, Markets from Culture., 2004 (Box 14)
  - Turner, Paul Venable, Mrs. Hoover's pueblo walls: the primitive and the modern in the Lou Henry Hoover House., 2004 (Box 14)
  - Urrutia, Matilde, My Life with Pablo Neruda., 2004 (Box 14)
  - Wang, Ban, Illuminations from the Past: Trauma, Memory, and History in Modern China., 2004 (Box 14)
  - Wang, Lingzhen, Personal matters: women's autobiographical practice in twentieth-century China., 2004 (Box 14)
  - Weber, Elisabeth, Questioning Judaism: interviews by Elisabeth Weber., 2004 (Box 15)
  - Weissberg, Herbert F., ed, Models of voting in presidential elections: the 2000 U.S. election., 2004 (Box 15)
  - Weitsman, Patricia A, Dangerous Alliances., 2004 (Box 15)
  - Wolf, Joan B, Harnessing the Holocaust; the politics of memory in France., 2004 (Box 15)
  - Yalom, Reid Samuel, Colonial noir: photographs from Mexico., 2004 (Box 15)
  - Yang, Dali L, Remaking the Chinese leviathan: market transition and the politics of governance in China., 2004 (Box 15)
  - Zelin, Madeleine, et. al., eds, Contract and property in early modern China., 2004 (Box 15)
  - Zhao, Suisheng, A nation-state by construction: dynamics of modern Chinese nationalism., 2004 (Box 15)
  - Ziarek, Krzysztof, The Force of Art., 2004 (Box 15)
- 2005
  - Agamben, Giorgio, The Time That Remains: A Commentary on the Letter to the Romans., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Amith, Jonathan D, The Mobius Strip: A Spatial History of Colonial Society in Guerrero, Mexico., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Ankersmit, Frank, Sublime Historical Experience., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Aspinall, Edward, Opposing Suharto:Compromise, Resistance, and Regime Change in Indonesia., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Atwill, David G., The Chinese Sultanate: Islam, Ethnicity, and the Panthay Rebellion in Sothwest China, 1865-1873., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Badiou, Alain, Handbook of Inaesthetics., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Baiocchi, Gianpaolo, Militants and Citizens: The Politics of Participatory Democracy in Porto Alegre., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Baker, David P., and Gerald K. Letendre, National Differences, Global Similarities: World Culture and the Future of Schooling., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Bender, John and Michael Marrinan, Regimes of Description: In the Archive of the Eighteenth Century., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Bendoly, Elliot, and F. Robert Jacobs, Strategic ERP: Extension and Use., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Bennett, Jill, Empathic Vision: Affect, Trauma and Contemporary Art., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Bornstein, Erica, The Spirit of Development: Protestant NGOs, Morality, and Economics in Zimbabwe., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Bray, David, Social Space and Governance in Urban China: The Danwei System from Origins to Reform., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Marshall, The Gothic Text., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Bryson, Bethany, Making Multiculturalism: Boundaries and Meaning in U.S. English Departments., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Camic, Charles, Philip S. Gorski, and David M. Trubek, Max Weber's Economy and Society: A Critical Companion., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Carlson, Allen, Unifying China, Integrating with the World: Securing Chinese Sovereignty in the Reform Era., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Cassedy, Steven, Dostoevsky's Religion., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Cavarero, Adriana, For More than One Voice: Toward a Philosophy of Vocal Expression., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Chen, Tina, Double Agency: Acts of Impersonation in Asian American Literature and Culture., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Chong, Alberto, and Florencio Lopez-de-Silanes, Privatization in Latin America: Myths and Reality., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Cohen, Myron L, Kinship, Contract, Community, and State:Anthropological Perspectives on China., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Dekker, George, The Fictions of Romantic Tourism: Radcliffe, Scott, and Mary Shelley., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Derrida, Jacques, On Touching - Jean-Luc Nancy., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Derrida, Jacques, Paper Machine., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Derrida, Jacques, Rogues: Two Essays on Reason., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Diamant, Neil J., Stanley B. Lubman and Kevin J. O'Brien, ed, Engaging the Law in China: State, Society, and Possibilities for Justice., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Dossani, Rafiq and Henry S. Rowen, Prospects for Peace in South Asia., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Espiritu, Augusto Fauni, Five Faces of Exile: The Nation and Filipino American Intellectuals., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Garcia, Maria Elena, Making Indigenous Citizens: Identity, Development, and Multicultural Activism in Peru., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Gerrits, Andrew W.M. and Dirk Jan Wolffram (ed.), Political Democracy and Ethnic Diversity in Modern European History., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Gheciu, Alexandra, NATO in the "New Europe": The Politics of International Socialization After the Cold War., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Goldstein, Avery, Rising to the Challenge:China's Grand Strategy and International Security., 2005 (Box 4)
  - Goodstein, Elizabeth S, Experience Without Qualities: Boredom and Modernity., 2005 (Box 4)
  - Greenhalgh, Susan, and Edwin A. Winckler, Governing China's Population: From Leninist to Neoliberal Biopolitics., 2005 (Box 4)
  - Guo, Qitao, Ritual Opera and Mercantile Lineage:The Confucian Transformation of Popular Cultures in Late Imperial Huizhou., 2005 (Box 4)
  - Hammond, Thomas H., Chris W. Bonneau, and Reginald S. Sheehan, Strategic Behavior and Policy Choice on the U.S. Supreme Court., 2005 (Box 4)
  - Hanley, Anne G, Native Capital: Financial Institutions and Economic Development in Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1850-1920., 2005 (Box 4)
  - Harrison, Henrietta, The Man Awakened from Dreams: One Man's Life in a North China Village, 1857, 1942., 2005 (Box 4)
  - Holohan, Anne, Networks of Democracy: Lessons from Kosovo for Afghanistan, Iraq, and Beyond., 2005 (Box 4)
  - Hsiung, Ping-Chen, A Tender Voyage: Children and Childhood in Late Imperial China., 2005 (Box 4)
  - Kamuf, Peggy, Book of Addresses., 2005 (Box 4)
  - Kemerer, Frank, Peter Sansom, and Jennifer Kemerer, California School Law., 2005 (Box 5)
  - Kim, Daniel Y, Writing Manhood in Black and Yellow., 2005 (Box 5)
  - Kleinberg-Levin, David Michael, Gestures of Ethical Life: Reading Holderlin's Question of Measure After Heidegger., 2005 (Box 5)
  - Kong, Shuyu, Consuming Literature: Bestsellers and the Commercialization of Literary Production in Contemporary China., 2005 (Box 5)
  - Lederman, Daniel, The Political Economy of Protection: Theory and the Chilean Experience., 2005 (Box 5)
  - Lederman, Daniel, William F. Maloney and Luis Serven, Lessons from NAFTA for Latin America and the Caribbean [hardcover]., 2005 (Box 5)
  - Lederman, Daniel, William F. Maloney, and Luis Serven, Lessons from NAFTA for Latin America and the Caribbean [softcover]., 2005 (Box 5)
  - Levy, Andre and Alex Weingrod, ed, Homelands and Diasporas: Holy Lands and Other Places., 2005 (Box 5)
  - Li, Huaiyin, Village Governance in North China, 1875-1936., 2005 (Box 5)
  - Loesberg, Jonathan, A Return to Aesthetics: Autonomy, Indifference, and Postmodernism., 2005 (Box 5)
  - Lu, Hanchao, Strret Criers: A Cultural History of Chinese Beggars., 2005 (Box 6)
  - Lundberg, Craig C., and Cheri A. Young, Foundations of Inquiry: Choices and Trade-Offs in the Organizational Sciences., 2005 (Box 6)
  - Lyons, John D, Before Imagination: Embodied Thought from Montaigne to Rousseau., 2005 (Box 6)
  - Manning, J. G., and Ian Morris, ed, The Ancient Economy: Evidence and Models., 2005 (Box 6)
  - Marme, Michael, Suzhou: Where the Goods of All the Provinces Converge., 2005 (Box 6)
  - Marrati, Paola, Genesis and Trace: Derrida Reading Husserl and Heidegger., 2005 (Box 6)
  - Miles, Raymond E., Grant Miles and Charles C. Snow, Collaborative Entrepreneurship:How Communities of Networked Firms Use Continuous Innovation to Create Economic Wealth., 2005 (Box 6)
  - Mondzain, Marie-Jose, Image, Icon, Economy: The Byzantine Origins of the Contemporary Imaginary., 2005 (Box 6)
  - Morgan, Stephen L, On the Edge of Commitment: Educational Attainment and Race in the United States., 2005 (Box 6)
  - Ocampo, Jose Antonio, ed, Beyond Reforms: Structural Dynamics and Macroeconomic Vulnerability., 2005 (Box 6)
  - Oishi, Nana, Women in Motion: Globalization, State Policies, and Labor Migration in Asia., 2005 (Box 6)
  - Palmquist, Peter E., and Thomas R. Kailbourn, Pioneer Photographers from the Mississippi to the continental Divide: A Biographical Dictionary, 1839 - 1865., 2005 (Box 7)
  - Parisi, Francesco and Vernon L. Smith, The Law and Economics of Irrational Behavior., 2005 (Box 7)
  - Park, Lisa Sun-Hee Park, Consuming Citizenship: Children of Asian Immigrant Entrepreneurs., 2005 (Box 7)
  - Parrenas, Rhacel Salazar, Children of Global Migration: Transnational Families and Gendered Woes., 2005 (Box 7)
  - Phillips, James, Heidegger's Volk:Between National Socialism and Poetry., 2005 (Box 7)
  - Phillips, Robert L, Pricing and Revenue Optimization., 2005 (Box 7)
  - Polhemus, Richard M, Lot's Daughter's: Sex, Redemption, and Women's Quest for Authority., 2005 (Box 8)
  - Ramakrishnan, S. Karthick, Democracy in Immigrant America: Changing Demographics and Political Participation., 2005 (Box 8)
  - Ramirez, Susan Elizabeth, To Feed and be Fed: The Cosmological Bases of Authority and Identity in the Andes., 2005 (Box 8)
  - Reardon-Anderson, James, Reluctant Pioneers:China's Expansion Northward 1644-1937., 2005 (Box 8)
  - Redish, Martin H, The Logic of Persecution: Free Expression and the McCarthy Era., 2005 (Box 8)
  - Rev, Istvan, Retroactive Justice: Prehistory of Post-Communism., 2005 (Box 8)
  - Rhode, Deborah L, Pro Bono in Principle and Practice: Public Service and the Professions., 2005 (Box 8)
  - Rottenberg, Elizabeth, Inheriting the Future: Legacies of Kant, Freud, and Flaubert., 2005 (Box 8)
  - Rousseau, David L, Democracy and War: Institutions, Norms, and the Evolution of International Conflict., 2005 (Box 8)
  - Sarat, Austin, and Christian Boulanger, ed, The Cultural Lives of Capital Punishment: Comparative Perspectives., 2005 (Box 8)
  - Sarat, Austin, and Stuart Scheingold (ed.), The Worlds Cause Lawyers Make: Structure and Agency in Legal Practice., 2005 (Box 9)
  - Sarat, Austin, Lawrence Douglas, and Martha Merrill Umphrey, Law on the Screen., 2005 (Box 9)
  - Sarat, Austin, Lawrence Douglas, and Martha Merrill Umphrey (ed.), The Limits of Law., 2005 (Box 9)
  - Schencking, J. Charles, Making Waves: Politics, Propaganda, and the Emergence of the Imperial Japanese Navy, 1868-1922., 2005 (Box 9)
  - Scherer, Nancy, Scoring Points: Politicians, Activists, and the Lower Federal Court Appointment Process., 2005 (Box 9)
  - Seel, Martin, Aesthetics of Appearing., 2005 (Box 9)
  - Senturk, Recep, Narrative Social Structure: Anatomy of the Hadith Transmission Network, 610-1505., 2005 (Box 9)
  - Siu, Lok C. D., Memories of a Future Home: Diasporic Citizenship of Chinese in Panama., 2005 (Box 9)
  - Stahl, Gunter K. and Mark E. Mendenhall, Mergers and Acquisitions: Managing Culture and Human Resources., 2005 (Box 9)
  - Stern, Sheldon M, The Week the World Stood Still: Inside the Secret Cuban Missile Crisis., 2005 (Box 9)
  - Strickmann, Michel, Chinese Poetry and Prophecy: The written Oracle in East Asia., 2005 (Box 10)
  - Svallfors, Stefan (ed.), Analyzing Inequality: Life Chances and Social Mobility in Comparative Perpsective., 2005 (Box 10)
  - Swedberg, Richard, The Max Weber Dictionary: Key Words and Central Concepts., 2005 (Box 10)
  - Swenson-Wright, John, Unequal Allies?: United States Security and Alliance Policy Toward Japan, 1945-1960., 2005 (Box 10)
  - Szalontai, Balazs, Kim Il Sung in the Krushchev Era: Soviet-DPRK Relations and the Roots of North Korean Despotism, 1953-1964., 2005 (Box 10)
  - Tang, Wenfang, Public Opinion and Political Change in China., 2005 (Box 10)
  - Tsu, Jing, Failure, Nationalism, and Literature: The Making of Modern Chinese Identity, 1895-1937., 2005 (Box 10)
  - Tushnet, Mark (ed.), Arguing Marbury v. Madison., 2005 (Box 10)
  - Umbach, Maiken, and Bernd Huppauf (eds.), Vernacular Modernism: Heimat, Globalization, and the Built Environment., 2005 (Box 10)
  - Van Gerven, Walter, The European Union: A Polity of States and Peoples., 2005 (Box 10)
  - Walter, Richard J, Politics and Urban Growth in Santiago, Chile 1891-1941., 2005 (Box 11)
  - Wang, Fei Ling, Organizing Through Division and Exclusion: China's Hukou System., 2005 (Box 11)
  - Wender, Melissa L, Lamentation as History: Narratives by Koreans in Japan, 1965-2000., 2005 (Box 11)
  - Wills, David, Matchbook: Essays in Deconstruction., 2005 (Box 11)
  - Wolf, Arthur P. and William H. Durham, Inbreeding, Incest, and the Incest Taboo: The State of Knowledge at the Turn of the Century., 2005 (Box 11)
  - Wolfreys, Julian, ed, The J. Hillis Miller Reader., 2005 (Box 11)
  - Zeitlin, Judith Francis, Cultural Politics in Colonial Tehuantepec: Community and State Among the Isthmus Zapotec, 1500-1750., 2005 (Box 11)
- 2006
  - Anderson, Terry L., Bruce L. Benson, and Thomas E. Flanagan, eds, Self-Determination: The Other Path for Native Americans., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Assmann, Jan, Religion and Cultural Memory., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Baeza, Cristian and Packard, Truman, Beyond Survival: Protecting Households from Health Shocks in Latin America., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Barbaras, Renaud, Desire and Distance: introduction to a Phenomenology of Perception., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Barkan, Elazar, and Alexander Karn, eds, Taking Wrongs Seriously: Apologies and Reconciliation., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Barman, Emily, Contesting Communities: The Transformation of Workplace Charity., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Basrur, Rajesh M, Minimum Deterrence and India's Nuclear Security., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Bass, Alan, Interpretation and Difference., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Baughman, John, Common Ground: Committee Politics in the U.S. House of Representatives., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Beinin, Joel, and Rebecca L. Stein (eds.), The Struggle for Sovereignty: Palestine and Israel 1993-2005., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Bennett, Nathan and Stephen A. Miles, Riding Shotgun: The Role of the COO., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Bennett, Robert W, Taming the Electoral College., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Bernstein, J.M, Against Voluptuous Bodies: Late Modernism and the Meaning of Painting., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Berri, David J., Martin B. Schmidt, and Stacey L. Brook, The Wages of Wins: Taking Measure of the Many Myths in Modern Sport., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Bloch, Ernst (trans. Anthony A. Nassar), Traces., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Brint, Steven, Schools and Societies (Second Edition)., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Burke, Peter J., ed, Contemporary Social Psychological Theories., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Canizares-Esguerra, Jorge, Nature, Empire and Nation- Explorations of Science in the Iberian World., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Canizares-Esguerra, Jorge, Puritan Conquistadors: Iberianizing the Atlantic, 1550-1700., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Carnochan, W.B, The Sad Story of Burton, Speke, and The Nile., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Carroll, Peter J, Between Heaven and Modernity: Reconstructing Suzhou, 1895-1937., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Chang, Shenglin, The Global Silicon Valley Home: Lives and Landscapes Within Taiwanese American Trans-Pacific Culture., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Chau, Adam Yuet, Miraculous Response: Doing Popular Religion in Contemporary China., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Cohen, Jeffrey E, Public Opinion in State Politics., 2006 (Box 3)
  - Cranston, Edwin A. (trans. w/commentary, appendixes, and notes), A Waka Anthology.Volume Two: Grasses of Remembrance. Part A., 2006 (Box 3)
  - Cranston, Edwin A. (trans. w/commentary, appendixes, and notes), A Waka Anthology.Volume Two: Grasses of Remembrance. Part B., 2006 (Box 3)
  - Crosnoe, Robert, Mexican Roots, American Schools: Helping Mexican Immigrant Children Succeed., 2006 (Box 3)
  - Cullather, Nick, Secret History- The CIA's Classified Account of its Operations in Guatemala, 1952-1954., 2006 (Box 3)
  - DeBernardi, Jean, The Way That Lives in the Heart: Chinese Popular Religion and Spirit Mediums in Penang, Malaysia., 2006 (Box 3)
  - Deegan-Krause, Kevin, Elected Affinities: Democracy and party competition in Slovakia and the Czech Republic., 2006 (Box 3)
  - Derrida, Jacques (trans. Laurent Milesi and Stefan Herbrechter), H. C. for Life, that is to Say..., 2006 (Box 3)
  - Diewald, Martin, Anne Goedicke, and Karl Ulrich Mayer, After the Fall of the Wall; Life Course in the Transformation of East Germany., 2006 (Box 3)